One Pace Premium
Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
Every time I look up to the sky after the rain
I think back to when I was a crybaby
I was chasing somebody's back blindly
Thinking "I want to be stronger"
The word "thank you" has faded into the wind now
Am I getting stronger?
I don't know the answer yet
That's why I'll keep walking ahead
So let's go
Without stopping
Without giving up to the flow of time
I'll keep getting back up
Because I don't want to lose something precious
The voice inside of me
keeps sustaining me
Wicked rain will get in my way
But I won't walk away
So let's go
Without stopping
Without giving up to the flow of time
I'll keep getting back up
Because I don't want to lose something precious
To the future I believe in...
A Gift to a New Era
The news has quickly spread around the world.
The Whitebeard Pirates have failed to rescue Roger’s son, Ace.
And their legendary captain, Whitebeard, has died.
We’re printing a special edition! Get to work!
This is an important announcement!
Following Fire Fist Ace, we can also confirm the death of Whitebeard!
I repeat:
At Marineford, Whitebeard has...
Whitebeard has...
Died!
The Whitebeard Pirates are done for, as well!
Now the war is over!
We can finally live in peace!
Those who have witnessed this unforgettable historic moment...
have been left speechless.
So you've passed on, Whitebeard.
The man who once rivaled...
the Pirate King on the high seas...
the captain of the Whitebeard Pirates...
and the legendary pirate...
Edward "Whitebeard" Newgate....
has died at the age of 72 in the fierce battle in Marineford Bay...
which broke out between his pirate armada and an alliance of the Navy and the Seven Royal Warlords of the Sea...
That damn bastard...
Marco. We all feel the same way...
but we have to retreat!
I know, Vista.
Don't just stand there! Get on the ship!
Did you forget our captain's final order?!
Jinbe! Hurry and take Ace's brother to safety!
Of course!
He sure was one stubborn bastard...
So he finally bit the dust?
So far, everything has gone exactly according to plan.
Well then, Captain...
Now, it's time to begin!
They're up to something again!
That Teach...
What's he planning to do with Pops?!
I'm about to present...
an amazing show that will astonish the entire world!
What's with that black shroud?!
Blackbeard and Whitebeard are both underneath it!
Now, I must ask that no one enters for the time being.
What are you trying to pull?!
He turned on us after pretending to have joined the Seven Royal Warlords of the Sea!
Don't let your guard down!
I'm looking forward to this.
If this fails, I suppose we'll have to disband.
Captain Buggy, where are you going?!
Are you stupid or what?! I'm running away, of course!
There's no way I can take Whitebeard's head now, is there?
Captain Buggy...
I failed!
I was too scared, and couldn't even approach him!
I was afraid!
Whitebeard... he was scary in his prime, and he's still scary after dying!
Just go ahead and think I'm pathetic if you want to!
This is where we part ways, you imbeciles!
Captain Buggy!
He's crying... Captain Buggy!
I get it... yesterday's enemies are friends today!
At some point, you felt sympathy for your rival Whitebeard as a fellow man!
Even though you were going to take his head!
And yet you're leaving without trying to make any excuses!
You truly are...
a man among men, just as we always thought you were!
You are too cool, Captain Buggy!
Please wait, Captain Buggy!
Take us with you!
Captain!
Hurry out to sea!
Luffy-kun...
Hang in there... You must survive...
in this world that Ace-san has already left behind...
on to tomorrow... and the day after...
Fire!
You must survive!
Jinbe... If I end up dying like this...
I hate to ask, but please take care of my brother...
I might have to refuse that request, Ace-san...
You mustn't overestimate me.
I'm not that kind-hearted.
He might be your brother, but in the world of pirates...
I will not lend a hand to anyone I don't think highly of, nor will I protect them.
Jinbe! Come onboard!
Sure!
This is...
Damn it... The ocean has been frozen!
We can't set sail!
Quickly, do something about it!
It's Admiral Aokiji!
Hold Aokiji back!
We have no choice... we must take another ship!
I said I wouldn't let him escape.
Just resign yourself to death, you imbecile!
Hand over Dragon’s son!
Akainu... isn't dead?!
I thought Pops finished him off!
He traveled underground...
by melting a path with his magma!
Jinbe!
That isn't happening!
I have already decided to protect this man, even at the cost of my life!
Then, I will not ask again.
Protect Ace's brother!
Ace's family is our family!
Get out of my way, you cowards!
Move aside, Jinbe!
Emporio Face-Growth Hormone
Iva-san. Allow me to help as well.
Great Scissors!
Vi will not let vyou lay one hand on Straw Hat-boy!
I will execute Dragon's son!
Hell... Wink!
Ever since Impel Down...
the damage that Straw Hat-boy has taken, both physically and mentally,
has long since gone past its limits!
If anything else were to happen to Straw Hat-boy now, while Vi'm here...
Vi will never be able to show vmy face to vmy comrade, Dragon, again!
I feel the same way.
Bring it on!
Right now, Vi am burning far, far hotter than vyou are!
Well then, ladies and gentlemen...
Thank you for waiting.
Captain Teach of the Blackbeard Pirates is proud to present...
the world's greatest show.
Please watch closely!
B-Blackbeard!
What was he doing in there?!
Whitebeard hasn't changed at all!
And Blackbeard is unchanged too!
Navy!
Allow me to show you my power!
Now, we are enemies once more.
Black Hole!
What's this?!
This is the power of my Dark-Dark Fruit!
And...
this is...
That stance!
That's...
the power of the Quake-Quake Fruit!
H-How did he use Whitebeard’s power?! He’s dead!
You did it, Captain!
That’s Pops’ earthquake power!
What's going on?! Damn that Teach!
The pull of darkness reverts all to nothing...
while the force of earthquakes destroys everything.
I've obtained it at last! Now, nobody is a match for me!
I am the strongest!
I don't know what he did...
but he's stolen Whitebeard's power!
How can that be possible?!
Then, the terror of the Quake-Quake Fruit...
still hasn't ended?!
I thought it was impossible to have the powers of two Devil Fruits!
It's definitely impossible for ordinary humans...
but... as you all know, Teach isn't quite normal.
His body is fundamentally different from an ordinary person's!
Is that what led to this?!
Hey, did you all see that?!
Let the whole world know this!
Peace-loving, boring commoners!
Marines! World Government! And pirates!
Is this some nightmare?
The future of this world has been decided!
Yes, from now on...
this is my era!
Navy HQ is crumbling to pieces!
Get out of here!
It's hopeless!
Is this... real?
Someone... please tell me this isn't true!
The fortress of justice, the Navy's base,
which has protected the oceans of the world for centuries...
How could it end up like this?!
After capturing Fire Fist Ace to trigger this war...
Blackbeard has stolen Whitebeard’s powers!
Behold, all you people of the world!
Look at me, and my power!
What will happen to the world?!
I can feel the power...
surging through me!
Damn it...
Such incredible power!
It appears that the world’s my oyster!
Damn him!
Hey! What's wrong?
What? Isn't anyone coming?
I'm willing to fight as many of you as you like, too...
What a shame!
Guess there's no helping it.
Then, first of all...
I guess I'll send Marineford to the bottom of the ocean!
What?!
A shockwave?!
We can just rebuild the fortress!
However...
this is the island at the very center of the world: Marineford!
Fleet Admiral...
Our presence here is significant to the citizens of the world...
who fear the villains infesting our waters!
Justice in the name of humanity shall not fall.
You will not so lightly speak of sinking this place.
You callow child!
Such admirable conviction!
Hey, Fleet Admiral-san?
Well then... listen!
Just try to protect it!
Damn it!
Now's vyour chance! Hurry!
Get Straw Hat-boy to safety!
Forgive me!
Inazuma!
Iva-sama!
Pirate scum!
Akainu!
Jinbe! Give up Dragon’s son!
The sea is my turf!
We can still escape!
Oh, no! It's frozen?!
Aokiji!
So you've come...
Looks like you've lost your escape route!
It didn't work...
Straw Hat Luffy!
You're mine!
Jinbe!
He pierced straight through Jinbe and hit Ace's brother!
Is he still alive?!
You’re in my way, Jinbe!
Luffy-kun... forgive me...
I let you get injured again...
This is no time to worry about others, you scum!
My aim was a little off because you interfered...
It would've been easier for him if I pierced his heart.
Don't you think so, Jinbe?
Are you still trying to protect him, with that hole in your chest?
You'll both die soon enough.
Crocodile!
Sables!
Someone catch him, and get him on a ship already!
Right...
Crocodile!
If you want to protect something, then you should do it right!
Don't let these guys keep doing whatever they want!
Catch him!
It's all over...
I'm so sorry for getting carried away, everyone.
The legend of Captain Buggy is over.
Thank you for supporting me.
Jinbe!
He's not falling back down...
What the hell is this?!
Captain Buggy!
You saved Straw Hat and Jinbe!
I knew it...
Captain Buggy... you just made it look like you were running away,
so that you could save your fellow escapee, Straw Hat, in his time of need!
How noble!
Your nobility is blinding me!
They're acting weird again...
Jinbe and Straw Hat!
How the hell did you end up flying through the air, covered in blood?
Hey, it sure is hot here...
M-Magma!
Thank you, Red Nose...
You saved us.
Still, I let Luffy-kun get another grave injury...
We must treat his wounds immediately!
Oh, shut up! I'm the one who needs help, you dumbass!
It's not like we can treat him up here...
Hey! Who're you calling Red Nose?!
They get in my way even to the very end!
Rose Rondo!
Another pack of vermin...
Do you all wish to die for Straw Hat's sake?
We've all seen his bottomless tenacity and power.
He's the man Ace protected, and Pops respected him!
It is our duty to send him on to the new era!
Every last one of you are fools!
Whitebeard Pirates!
Akainu.
The terrible danger you see in the one you want to kill...
the immense potential we see in the one we want to save...
Ain't they one and the same?!
I can't believe you got me involved again!
Are you listening to me?
Hey, J-Jinbe?
You're unconscious?!
Hey, where should I go now?!
Hey!
Alive or dead, that bastard’s in hell.
Just leave him to suffer!
I guess nothing I say will stop you at this point.
Do your worst!
I-It's hopeless...
Sengoku and Blackbeard are over there...
And Akainu and the commanders are over there...
The battle will never end!
Captain Buggy! Do something!
Like hell, you idiots!
What the...
It's a ship!
That's a submarine!
Whose ship is that?
Bring Straw Hatter over here!
"Straw Hatter"? That sure is a weird way to address a guy...
Who are you, kid?!
Straw Hatter and I will probably be enemies someday...
but I have nothing against him.
It'd be no fun to let him die here.
Captain of the Heart Pirates Trafalgar Law
I'll get him out of here. Hand him over!
What?!
I'm a doctor!
Editing, Sewil
Quality Control, Grug, Pepperjack
Timing, Galaxy 9000
Translation, Yibis
Visual Effects, Datenshi, KaitouYahiko
Graphics, Datenshi
Karaoke, KaitouYahiko
Soundtracking, Halee
Raws, Netflix